♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we’ve got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright
on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we’ll
withstand it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there
when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we
will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko
stronger after all ♪
(LAUGHING)
I’ve never seen her laugh so much.
You’re telling me,
I’ve never seen her laugh at all!
(LAUGHING)
The gas I’ve just inhaled
in this small quantity
is called nitrogen protoxide,
N2O, ha-ha-ha!
for those of you interested
in chemistry, of course, heh ha!
Although, it’s better known
as laughing gas, ha ha-ha ha ha ha!
You can see why this gas
is sometimes used in hospitals
to relax patients who are
going to be operated on, hah hah ha ha ha!
Not a bad idea.
Nothing like a laughing attack
after an appendix attack.
(LAUGHING)
Let’s try to stay serious!
In strong doses, this gas
can be highly toxic!
In provoking very serious
modifications in perception,
and even lesions in the
nervous system,
sometimes even fatal,
so one can, as the saying goes,
literally die laughing!
Hahahahahahahahaha!
Only one thing can
neutralize the gas, hah! Water.
All you need is one drop
to volatilize it!
Enough of that.
Get out a sheet of paper
for a surprise quiz.
She’s been sulking
like that for two days.
Nothing seem to cheer her up.
I can try some of my jokes on her.
That might do the trick!
I’m not saying you don’t have
a good sense of humor, Odd,
but I’d rather go and talk to her.
You think Ulrich will
manage to get her to smile?
Yeah, as sure as Julia Roberts
is gonna call and invite me out to dinner.
Yeah, I think you’re right.
She’s really down.
Please, Ulrich, leave me alone.
I really don’t feel like talking.
But I feel like talking.
And with you.
If you like talking so much,
talk to yourself, okay?
Don’t worry, Ulrich!
Not all girls are like Yumi!
Yeah, that’s a shame.
Hey, wait, Ulrich!
Are you coming tomorrow?
To the rehearsal? Huh?
Yeah, I’ll be there,
but not for you, it’s for Odd.
For your information, It’s thanks to me
that Odd’s playing the music!
Mhmm.
And if you want to be
part of the group,
the role of Romeo
is just ideal for you!
And I suppose that
you, of course, are Juliet.
Yes! That’s perfect casting,
don’t you think?
Well, it’s a perfect reason
for me not to play Romeo.
(TROMBONE)
(SINISTER MUSIC)
(RINGS)
Oh, it’s you, darling!
I said to myself, “We couldn’t stay
angry with each other for--”
Oh…hello, Ulrich.
Good evening, mam.
I wanted to talk to Yumi.
What about your dad? Where is he?
Staying with a friend from work.
And what was it your parents
argued about, huh?
I have no idea. My mother
tried to tell me, but, I…
I didn’t understand,
and I’m not sure she did either.
Yeah, those arguments are the worst.
I’m really glad that you came.
Thanks, Ulrich.
You know how to cheer someone up.
It’s strange that they’re
mad at each other.
Yumi and Ulrich
always get along so well.
You know, Aelita, very often
people who get along well have fights.
Really?
What about you and I?
Why don’t we ever fight?
You and I?
Well, I don’t know, really…
Anyway, XANA’s been quiet lately.
Too quiet, don’t you think?
What I worry most about
are the risks you all take.
You know, XANA would
really love to get rid of you.
Don’t worry, the only one of us
who’s in any real danger today is Odd.
He’s rehearsing with Sissi.
Now that’s what I call a risk!
(SLOW ROMANTIC MUSIC)
I don’t know if she’ll appear tonight,
but…uh, let’s see, oh!
I know she loves me! Mhmm.
That’s awful!
It’s about as flat as a pancake!
It’s not me, it’s the lines!
What’s wrong with the lines, hm!
Well--!
I can’t even say ’em!
There’s nothing
wrong with them, it’s you!
You know how long
I spent on the text?
Well, my guess would be
about 30 seconds!
I dare you to repeat that!
Look, I’d rather you repeated
your lines, Herb, and with feeling!
Nicholas, there’s no reason
for you to be on stage,
and, Odd, you’re playing
much too fast!
Sure, if I play a little slower,
it’ll give me more than enough
time to take a little nap!
Hey, keep all your bad jokes
for yourself, huh!
Okay, now let’s take it again
from the top, and try to concentrate!
(ROMANTIC MUSIC)
I don’t know if she’ll appear tonight…
but I know--
but I don't know if she loves me.
Oh, a guard! On guard!
HEH-HAH-HA-HA-HA-HA-HA-HA!
What is going on!
What is it now, Odd!
Come on, it wasn’t that bad!
You’re not gonna want to laugh
when I get through with you!
Get him, Sissi!
AH-HA-HA-HA-HA-HA-HA-HA-HA!
AAH-HA-HA-HA-HAHAHAHA!
AAH-HA-HA--!
(COUGHING)
And don’t bother coming tomorrow, Odd!
We’re preforming a tragedy,
not a musical comedy!
Huh? Hey, wait, uh…
(RINGS)
Yumi!
Good evening, sir.
I would like to see my father.
Uh, just a second. I’ll get him.
Uh, would you know why
your mother and father
aren’t talking to each other?
I was afraid of that.
Yum! How nice to see you. Come in.
Daddy, I-I want you to come home.
Listen, Yumi.
This is between your mother and me,
and she and I have got to work it out.
Oh, yeah? And how?
You’re not even willing
to talk to each other!
I think I’ve got an idea.
It was crazy.
I really didn’t feel like laughing at all,
but it was impossible to stop!
As soon as Sissi poured water on me,
that was it, I stopped immediately.
N2O. Laughing gas.
Miss Hertz said that the only thing
that could volatilize it was water.
You think this could be a XANA thing?
You never know.
Aelita, keep looking around.
Okay, but no pulsations for now.
Let’s go see if the bottle of laughing gas
Miss Hertz used is still in the science room.
Kiwi, you stay here.
(BARKS)
If you’ve come to apologize,
Odd, don’t bother!
Oh. Oh, it you, Ulrich.
What are you doing here?
Well, I was wondering, Sissi,
if there was a part, even a little one
that Yumi could play.
And why would I want
to give Yumi a part?
Forget that I even asked. Goodbye.
No, Ulrich, wait! I…
Hm?
There just might be a solution.
Aelita and me, we never fight.
You think that’s normal?
Huh?
Y-Yeah, no…how do I know?
You think we’d fight
if she lived here in our world?
What I do think is we’re gonna
get caught if you don’t hurry up!
Bingo.
It’s empty.
Guess we ran out of gas…
if you pardon the expression.
Okay, listen.
Tomorrow, we’ll go to the factory
instead of the play and check things out.
Aelita?
Hey, Aelita, can you hear me?
Communication refused.
Okay, Jeremie.
I’m ready to go.
Mhmm.
Aaaaaah!
Thank heavens, a tower! Just in time!
I’ll transfer you to the mountain region.
I've stpotted some monsters there.
The tower can't be far.
Transfer Odd.
Scanner Odd.
Virtualization.
Data transfer problem.
I feel very weak, Jeremie.
Did anything happen during the transfer?
Jeremie?
Can you hear me, Jeremie?
Jeremie, can you hear me?
Jeremie?
Jeremie!
Well, there we are.
I put cue lines up everywhere, Ulrich.
You’ll see, you’ll make a perfect Romeo.
Hey, I’m doing it for you.
She’s right, you know.
You do make a “perfect Romeo”
Okay, Yumi.
Now come with me
so I can show you your costume.
I can’t believe you stole my part.
It isn’t my fault, Herb, I swear.
I wonder why I don’t just slug you.
Fear, maybe?
Please tell me I don’t
look too dumb, huh?
Don’t be silly, you look really stunning.
I hope we’re not
doing this for nothing.
Did you talk to your folks?
Yeah, they’re gonna come.
Both of them? How’d you do it?
I lied.
I told each one of them
that the other wasn’t gonna come.
Hah.
Adults can be such
children sometimes, huh?
Aah!
Uh-oh…
This is not a good time
to desert me, Jeremie.
The welcoming committee
looks really mean,
and I’m not feeling too good.
Jeremie?
Virtual envelope damaged.
Things don’t look so good…
Aah!
Good evening.
There’s my mother.
I suppose your husband is
meeting you here tonight?
Uh, no, my husband isn’t able to come.
He’s, uh, not feeling well!
Hmm.
Oh, Mr. Ishiyama!
I’m delighted to see that you’re
feeling better already!
Uh, feeling better?
Well, your wife has just arrived.
My wife…is here?
You’re not out of the woods yet.
I’m too weak to fight them.
I’ll have to trick them.
Here we go!
Laser arrow!
Aelita, are you there?
Odd?
Hurry up!
XANA might send us more monsters!
We’d better not stay here!
Uh, I, um, I…
I don’t know if she will--
she will appear tonight!
At her balcony!
I'm…
Huh?
What does it say?
I can’t read it.
Uh…
Does she…
what does it say?
Oh! Oh, right! Uh…
Does she love me!
Anyway, I think she does!
Enter guard? Huh?
En garde, guard!
(LAUGHTER)
Hide, hide!
Look, it’s Yumi!
Boy, they’re tough.
Oh, no. Where are my next lines?
I see ’em.
Go away!
There must’ve been a problem
during the transfer.
I feel weaker and weaker.
Odd, are you okay?
Yeah, I’ll be just fine.
(PULSING)
You’ve gotta hang on, Odd.
You see the pulsations?
The tower that XANA
activated can’t be too far.
I hope not.
Odd!
Hey, what’s that?
Oh, no!
That’s all we needed.
A labyrinth.
Ah, at last you’re here!
You who is so fair and, uh, fair!
We’ve been here before, I’m sure.
We’re lost.
Without Jeremie’s help, it’s all over.
Well, Jeremie, how do you want to die?
Freezing or laughing?
I gotta do something.
I can’t hang on any longer.
You who lights up my days!
You who is the sunshine of my nights!
This is awful!
He’s massacring my text, huh!
Even you were better!
Oh, my Romeo!
You are my bow!
Oh, Romeo, cara mio amore mio!
Uh…
D’HAHA! HA-HA-HA-HA!
(LAUGHTER)
Huh!
What did I say!
What’s so funny!?
Everyone is laughing at me now!
(COUGHING)
It’s not normal!
They’re going to choke!
We’ve got to find a way to help!
I know what to do.
What happened?
It was like I was being controlled.
What’s he talking about?
This thing is afraid of water.
Sissi, gimmie that! Fast!
You could say please!
Sissi! Gimmie that bottle,
will you? Hurry up!
Come on.
(WHEEZING)
Yumi, you okay?
Oh, darling, we were so frightened!
Aah! Ah! Aha!
Ulrich!
(LAUGHS)
What’s going on?
What’s the matter with her?
(LAUGHS)
We’re almost there, Aelita.
I just had a psychic vision.
You have to go left, you hear?
And don’t wait for me.
I’m too weak to go.
Okay, Odd. I’ll get there.
Don’t worry.
Oh, I’m not worried.
(WHEEZING)
Water!
And call for help!
Please hurry!
Return to the past, now.
You’ve gotta be kidding.
I won’t ever be part of that
dumb play again.
Well, at least now we know
how to get your folks together.
I’m never gonna wear
that stupid costume again!
I agree.
Hm?
I’ve got a better idea.
As for Ulrich, I’m really sorry,
but you’re going to have to
sacrifice yourself one more time.
At least that way we can
finally see you as Romeo!
Let’s face it, a nice laughing fit
is good for you from time to time!
I don’t know if she’ll
appear tonight on her balcony,
But I’m certain, um…
I’m certain she…she loves me!
And I know I love her very much.
And I know I love her very much!
Aah, no, a guard!
(LAUGHTER)
Where’s Yumi?
Isn’t she supposed to be in the play?
(LAUGHTER)
It worked!
What’s the matter now!
What happened?
Why are you all laughing?
You don’t understand drama!
This is not a comedy,
it’s a great tragedy!
(APPLAUSE)
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED BY
REDDIT.COM/R/CODELYOKO